<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Steve's Blog</title><link>https://stevehipwell.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Steve's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 16:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stevehipwell.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Give Blog another Chance</title><link>https://stevehipwell.github.io/post/give-blog-another-chance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stevehipwell.github.io/post/give-blog-another-chance/</guid><description>After two years of inactivity from my first post it might be reasonably assumed that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to follow through with my plan to start blogging! *
* Ironically almost 6 months after starting to write this post I hadn&amp;rsquo;t finished it let alone added any actual content!</description></item><item><title>Give Blog a Chance</title><link>https://stevehipwell.github.io/post/give-blog-a-chance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 17:43:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://stevehipwell.github.io/post/give-blog-a-chance/</guid><description>So I&amp;rsquo;m going to give this blogging thing a go; I&amp;rsquo;ve attempted to write blog posts on a number of occasions but I&amp;rsquo;ve never managed to finish one and publish it. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why I think this time will be any different but here goes&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;m aiming to focus on interesting things that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on, thoughts that I have, great projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve come across, and random stuff that interests me.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://stevehipwell.github.io/page/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stevehipwell.github.io/page/about/</guid><description>I work as a Senior Systems Architect for Lexis Nexis Risk Solutions Group where I&amp;rsquo;m focused on our Kubernetes and cloud native architecture. I love to geek out on Kubernetes and the adjacent technologies and love discussing them with others. Outside of the actual technology I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about platform engineering and am an adherent of the &amp;ldquo;everything as code&amp;rdquo; movement.
In my spare time I enjoy sports, technology, DIY and craft beer!</description></item></channel></rss>